metromela.com 2009-04-26

# Metromela home page

Privacy Policy

This privacy policy describes how we handle your personal information. We collect, use and share personal information to help MetroMela website work.

We collect… 

  * Name,e-mail address, contact information, demographic profile, interests and preferences, opinions and depending on the service used, sometimes financial information. You can choose to provide demographic information such as occupation, education and gender to us. However, we encourage you to submit this information so that we can customize your experience on our site.
  * Computer sign-on data, statistics on page views, traffic to and from MetroMela and ad data. 
  * Other information including users' IP addresses and standard web log information. 
  * Friend's name and e-mail address, in case you use our referral service. 

We use it to…  

  * Provide services.
  * Resolve disputes, collect fees and troubleshoot problems.
  * Enforce our policies.
  * Customize users' experience, measure interest in our services and inform users about services and updates.
  * Communicate marketing and promotional offers. 
  * Notify users who win any contest.
  * Preserve social history as governed by existing law or policy.

Information thus collected shall not directly or indirectly violate the laws of the country of your residence or that of the person(s) to whom the material is made available. 

Disclosure…

We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that a posting or other content violates others' rights, or protect anyone's rights, property or safety. We will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information to third parties unless we have your permission. We will share it to provide products or services you've requested, to help investigate or prevent illegal activities, violation of metromela.com Terms of Use or for any other legal issues.

We may also share personal information with - 

  * Corporate affiliates who help detect and prevent potentially illegal acts and provide joint services.
  * Service providers who help with our business operations.
  * Carefully screened third party service providers who wish to provide our users with offers of value.

Using Information from MetroMela…

You may use personal information gathered from MetroMela only to follow up with another user about a specific posting; not to send spam. Any personal information collected from another user has to be with that user’s expressed permission. 

Access, Modification and Deletion… 

You can review, modify or erase your personal information by reviewing your posting or account status page. We delete personal information when we no longer need it for the purposes we described earlier. 

Security… 

We use several tools such as encryption, passwords and physical security to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure, but we do not guarantee the security of your personal information. 

General… 

We may update this policy at any time, with updates taking effect when you next use any MetroMela service. If we or our corporate affiliates are involved in a merger or acquisition, we may share personal information with another company, but this policy will continue to apply. You can send questions about this policy to [privacy@metromela.com.](mailto:privacy@metromela.com)

Copyright © 2007-2008 MetroMela Internet Services Pvt Ltd. All Rights Reserved.
